Hello friends, I am Farida. Welcome to RTI SK's
news agency. Let's
see today's big news. Hello friends,
I am Farida. You are watching Samach Khabar Hindi
TV News. At this time, we are present
in Malad West Malvani. In the Math
School, helmets are being distributed to the children.
What is the
motive behind this? Why is it being distributed? On
whose behalf is it being done? Sir is present with us.
Let's know from him. Sir, tell me your name.
My name is Vinay Parve and I am from Seva
Sec Foundation, Mumbai. ICICI
Labad has been running a project called Right to the Safety
since 2018 and till now,
under this project, they plan to distribute
12,000 helmets among two lakh helmet distributors.
What is the situation these days that road accidents have
increased a lot and if we
compare it with 108 countries, then the maximum
road accidents happen in our India
and this project is being done for the safety of children and their parents.
Because
helmets of the size of children from class 3rd to 7th are
not always available in the market, so
ICICI Ltd has specially designed these helmets, this is done
every year,
it is given every year since 2018, so these
are helmets specially designed for children and the documents that are taken from the
distributor for free, those
documents are taken in which
RC book and driving license are taken
and these helmets are distributed only to those whose documents are clear, in
whose name the vehicle is registered,
in which schools have you distributed till now,
yes, apart from St. Matthew,
we have distributed in three schools
and out of those two schools are from Mumbai and the
third school is a school in Kalyan,
so last year we distributed these helmets to 12000 helmet
distributors, to all the
schools within the distributor region and whose parents have
valid documents, we are going to
distribute these helmets, thank
you sir, in this way you can see
Along with the children, the parents can also have
helmets in their hands. Now let's see how much the
children maintain their safety.
[Music]
Ch
S
[Music]
Do you have an NGO and
need donations to work but are
unable to get donations due to lack of 12 ATG certificate, then
contact the RTI SK agency. You can get the
12 ATG certificate made by contacting the RTI SK agency.